Guide to the New York Community Trust Records 1919-2024 MS 3246
New-York Historical Society
- Series 3: Historical materials (PARTIALLY RESTRICTED), 1919-2024
  - Sub-series 3: Annual reports, 1924-2023
    - Annual reports, 1924-1947 (Offsite-box 3.3.1, Folder 1-29)
      Folder 2: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 2, What Bankers Are Saying about the Community Trust, n.d.
      Folder 3: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 4, What the Community Trust Is and How to Use It, n.d.
      Folder 4: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 5, The Community Trust As Viewed by Lawyers, ca. 1924
      Folder 5: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 6, Four Notable Addresses on the Community Trust (Garfield, Finley, Ayres, Baker), n.d.
      Folder 6: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 9, Frozen Funds, n.d.
      Folder 7: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 11, Forms, n.d.
      Folder 8: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no.12, ca. 1927
      Folder 9: Annual report, 1927
      Folder 10: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 13, Till the End of Time, 1928
      Folder 11: Annual report (letter from Ralph Hayes to Winthrop W. Aldrich, Chairman, Trustees Committee, NYCT), 1930
      Folder 12: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 14, The Community Trust in Operation, 1931
      Folder 13: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 15, The Community Trust: Its Origin and Function, ca. 1931
      Folder 14: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 16, Thirty-three Funds, 1932
      Folder 15: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 17, Tired Endowments and Others, 1933
      Folder 16: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 18, The Administration of Charitable Funds, 1934
      Folder 17: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 20, Forty Funds, 1935
      Folder 18: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 21, Enduring Memorials: The Administering of Charitable Trusts, 1936
      Folder 19: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 22, Envoys Everlasting, 1937
      Folder 20: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 23, Fifty Funds, 1938
      Folder 21: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 24, As Long As Time, 1939
      Folder 22: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 25, Money At Work, 1940
      Folder 23: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 26, The First Ten Million, 1941
      Folder 24: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 27, Sixty Funds, 1942
      Folder 25: The Story of the Community Trust, issue no. 28, For Tomorrow, 1943
      Folder 26: The Story of the Community Trust, Common Wealth, 1944
      Folder 27: Annual report, Remembrance Kept, 1945
      Folder 28: Annual report, Unfinished Business, 1946
      Folder 29: Annual report, The Noblest of Shrines,... A Home in the Minds of Men, 1947
    - Annual reports, 1948-1962 (Offsite-box 3.3.2, Folder 1-15)
      Folder 1: Annual report, 100 Funds, 1948
      Folder 2: Annual report, Growth of a Heritage, 1949
      Folder 3: Annual report,... In Progress, 1950
      Folder 4: Annual report, New Look, 1951
      Folder 5: Annual report, Till Now, 1952
      Folder 6: Annual report, Long Harvest, 1953
      Folder 7: Annual report, All Through the Years, 1954
      Folder 8: Annual report,... For a Long Time, 1955
      Folder 9: Annual report, Past Is Prologue, 1956
      Folder 10: Annual report, Creating and Managing Charitable Funds, 1957
      Folder 11: Annual report, Administering Philanthropic Funds, 1958
      Folder 12: Annual report, The Management of Charitable Funds, 1959
      Folder 13: Annual report, 150 Funds At Work, 1960
      Folder 14: Annual report, 1961
      Folder 15: Annual report, 1962
    - Annual reports, 1963-1981 (Offsite-box 3.3.3)
    - Annual reports, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 3.3.4)
    - Annual reports, 1994-2003 (Offsite-box 3.3.5)
    - Annual reports, 2004-2013 (Offsite-box 3.3.6)
    - Annual reports, 2014-2023 (Offsite-box 3.3.7)
  - Sub-series 4: Affiliates (PARTIALLY RESTRICTED), 1936-2022
    Materials in some boxes in this sub-series are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Fairfield County Cooperative Foundation (RESTRICTED), 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 3.4.1.1, Folder 1-6)
      Folder 1: Official documents; Board of Directors, Minutes, October 1982-December 1985
      Folder 2: Board of Directors, Minutes, April 1986-June 1990
      Folder 3: Board of Directors, Minutes, July 1990-March 1992
      Folder 4: Board of Directors, Dockets, October 1982-October 1983
      Folder 5: Board of Directors, Dockets, April 1984-April 1985
      Folder 6: Board of Directors, Dockets, October 1985-October 1986
      Materials in Box 3.4.1.1 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Fairfield County Cooperative Foundation (RESTRICTED), 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 3.4.1.2, Folder 1-3)
      Folder 1: Board of Directors, Dockets, April 1987-February 1988
      Folder 2: Board of Directors, Dockets, May 1988-May 1989
      Folder 3: Board of Directors, Dockets, March-June 1990
      Materials in Box 3.4.1.2 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Long Island Community Foundation, 1977-2022 (Offsite-box 3.4.2, Folder 1-18)
      Folder 1: LICF -- History, development, and programs, 1977-2008
      Folder 2: LICF -- NYCT Distribution Committee/CFI Board of Directors meeting agendas, memoranda re: distribution matters, grants reports, administrative matters, investments, 1977-1978 (RESTRICTED)
      Folder 3: LICF -- Pocket Guide to Intelligent Giving – 22 Ways to Use the Long Island Community Foundation, 1978, 1982
      Folder 4: LICF -- A History of Jericho (adaptation) by Larry Leicht, 1978; The Elias Hicks House (Home of Long Island Community Foundation), ca. 2000
      Folder 5: LICF -- Brochures, 1979-2006
      Folder 6: LICF -- Newsletters, 1985-2009
      Folder 7: LICF -- Newsletter, 2012-2021
      Folder 8: LICF -- Grants made, 1986-2006
      Folder 9: LICF -- Watercolor painting of LICF sign by Daley, 1991
      Folder 10: LICF -- Grant application guidelines, 1992, 2001
      Folder 11: LICF -- Seminars offered by Long Island Community Foundation, 1993, 1998
      Folder 12: LICF -- Remarks by Suzy D. Sonenberg, President of LICF, at the annual meeting of the Family Service League of Suffolk County, ca. 1994
      Folder 13: LICF -- Advertising and publicity, 1997, 2004-2008, n.d.
      Folder 14: LICF -- What Everyone Should Know about Wills; Wills and Estate Planning Workbook, 1999
      Folder 15: LICF -- Annual reports, 1999-2022
      Folder 16: LICF -- A Report on the Unrestricted Grants Program of the Long Island Community Foundation, by Madeline Lee Consulting Services, May 2004 (RESTRICTED)
      Folder 17: LICF -- Long Island Community Foundation Supports All For The East End (AFTEE), reprinted from Networking, October 2015
      Folder 18: LICF -- Donor stories: Ventures in Philanthropy; Making a Difference on Long Island, n.d.
      Materials in Folders 2 and 16 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Westchester Community Foundation, 1971-2022 (Offsite-box 3.4.3, Folder 1-16)
      Folder 1: WCF -- History of the Westchester Foundation, June 18, 1971
      Folder 2: WCF -- Pocket Guide to Intelligent Giving: 22 Ways to Use the Westchester Community Foundation, 1978, 1982
      Folder 3: WCF -- Summary of grants made by Westchester Community Foundation, 1979-1980
      Folder 4: WCF -- Reports for 1983 and 1984 (includes examples of grants funded), 1983-1984
      Folder 5: WCF -- Brochures, 1987, n.d.
      Folder 6: WCF -- Understanding the Westchester Community Foundation, May 1989
      Folder 7: WCF -- Event invitations, 1989-1994
      Folder 8: WCF -- Westchester Fund for Women and Girls Events, 1995-2008
      Folder 9: WCF -- Annual reports, 1999-2021
      Folder 10: WCF -- The Apoyo Fund, information packet, 2004-2005
      Folder 11: WCF -- Westchester Fund for Women and Girls 10th anniversary awards breakfast, November 4, 2005
      Folder 12: WCF -- The Apoyo Fund, invitations to events, 2006-2007
      Folder 13: WCF -- Newsletters, 2008-2022
      Folder 14: WCF -- Edwin Irving Johnson Scholarship, brochure, n.d.
      Folder 15: WCF -- Gathering Growing Granting Charitable Funds", brochure, n.d.
      Folder 16: WCF -- Where Can You Make a Difference?, brochure, n.d.
  - Sub-series 5: Donor biographical files, n.d.
    Existence and Location of Originals
    Active donor files retained by the New York Community Trust.
    - Donor biographical brochures (A-Y) (Offsite-box 3.5)
  - Sub-series 6: Oral history interviews, 2019-2021
    - Oral history interviews, 2019-2021 (Offsite-box 3.6.1, Folder 1-5)
      Folder 1: NYCT Oral History Project: Bob Edgar, interviewed by Katherine Snyder, The Narrative Trust, October 28. 2019
      Folder 2: NYCT Oral History Project: Pat Jenny, interviewed by Melanie Shorin, The Narrative Trust, December 12, 2019
      Folder 3: NYCT Oral History Project: Robert M. Kaufman, interviewed by Melanie Shorin, The Narrative Trust, January 28, 2019
      Folder 4: NYCT Oral History Project: Sam Polk, interviewed by Melanie Shorin, The Narrative Trust, August 7, 2019
      Folder 5: NYCT Oral History Project: Jane Wilton, interviewed by Katherine Snyder, The Narrative Trust, May 12, 2021
  - Sub-series 7: Slutsky files (PARTIALLY RESTRICTED), 1983-2022
    - Slutsky files, 1983-2016 (Offsite-box 3.7.1, Folder 1-7)
      Folder 1: Speeches, 1983-1989
      Folder 2: Speeches, 1990-1993
      Folder 3: Speeches, 1994-1998
      Folder 4: Speeches, 1999-2001
      Folder 5: Speeches, 2002-2004
      Folder 6: Speeches, 2005-2013
      Folder 7: Speeches, 2014-2016
    - Slutsky files (PARTIALLY RESTRICTED), 1983-2022 (Offsite-box 3.7.2, Folder 1-8)
      Folder 1: Speeches, 2017-2022
      Folder 2: Distribution Committee presentations, 1983-1986 (RESTRICTED)
      Folder 3: Slutsky, Lorie A. Writing, interviews, comments, 1986-2022
      Folder 4: Future Shock: The Case for Endowment, by Lorie A. Slutsky and Ani F. Hurwitz (chapter 6, Here for Good: Community Foundations and the Challenges of the 21st Century, Terry Mazany and David C. Petty, editors, 2014
      Folder 5: Slutsky, Lorie. Speech notes, information, facts, quotes
      Folder 6: Slutsky – Misspelled
      Folder 7: Slutsky, Lorie A. Retirement, announcement, correspondence, celebration at New-York Historical Society, April 2021-2022
      Folder 8: It's Been a Privilege: A Book of Memories for Lorie A. Slutsky from Those Who Had the Privilege to Work with Her (retirement gift book published by NYCT), June 2022
      Materials in Folder 2 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Slutsky files, 1976-2020 (Offsite-box 3.7.3, Folder 1-8)
      Folder 1: Slutsky, Lorie A. CVs, bios, press releases, 1983-2019
      Folder 2: Congratulations – Transition to President of NYCT, December 1988-January 1989
      Folder 3: Slutsky, Lorie A. Honorary doctorate, Colgate University, May 18, 2014
      Folder 4: New York City Council citation: NYCT & Lorie A. Slutsky, Celebrating Women, New York Women's Foundation, May 10, 2018
      Folder 5: Slutsky, Lorie A. Kudos, awards, appreciation, 1976-1989
      Folder 6: Slutsky, Lorie A. Kudos, awards, appreciation, 1991-2013
      Folder 7: Slutsky, Lorie A. Kudos, awards, appreciation, 2014-2016
      Folder 8: Slutsky, Lorie A. Kudos, awards, appreciation, 2017-2020
    - Slutsky files, memoranda (RESTRICTED), 1985-2022 (Offsite-box 3.7.4)
      Materials in Box 3.7.4 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Slutsky files, correspondence (RESTRICTED), 1986-2021 (Offsite-box 3.7.5)
      Materials in Box 3.7.5 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Slutsky files, correspondence (RESTRICTED), 1994-2021 (Offsite-box 3.7.6)
      Materials in Box 3.7.6 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
  - Sub-series 8: Silberman Fund (RESTRICTED), 1964-2011
    Materials in Sub-series 8: Silberman Fund are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Silberman Fund (RESTRICTED), 1951-1984 (Offsite-box 3.8.1, Folder 1-6)
      Folder 1: Silberman Fund -- Charter, by-laws, tax-exemption, name change, 1951-1959
      Folder 2: Meeting minutes, Grant Committee, 1964-1972
      Folder 3: Meeting minutes, Grant Committee, 1973-1984
      Folder 4: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 1951-1965
      Folder 5: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 1966-1976
      Folder 6: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 1977-1983
      Materials in Box 3.8.1 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Silberman Fund (RESTRICTED), 1984-2011 (Offsite-box 3.8.2, Folder 1-5)
      Folder 1: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 1984-1987
      Folder 2: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 1988-1991
      Folder 3: By-laws, agreements, tax rulings, CFI resolution, 1992-1997
      Folder 4: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 1992-2002
      Folder 5: Meeting minutes, Board of Directors, 2003-2011
      Materials in Box 3.8.2 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Silberman Fund (RESTRICTED), 1992-2003 (Offsite-box 3.8.3, Folder 1-6)
      Folder 1: Dockets, Board of Directors, October 1992-June 1994
      Folder 2: Dockets, Board of Directors, January 1995-June 1996
      Folder 3: Dockets, Board of Directors, January 1997-July 1998
      Folder 4: Dockets, Board of Directors, January 1999-October 2000
      Folder 5: Dockets, Board of Directors, April-October 2001
      Folder 6: Dockets, Board of Directors, April 2002-October 2003
      Materials in Box 3.8.3 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Silberman Fund (RESTRICTED), 1971-2011 (Offsite-box 3.8.4, Folder 1-13)
      Folder 1: Dockets, Board of Directors, March-November 2004
      Folder 2: Dockets, Board of Directors, January-November 2005
      Folder 3: Dockets, Board of Directors, March 2006-June 2007
      Folder 4: Dockets, Board of Directors, January 2008-June 2010
      Folder 5: Dockets, Board of Directors, June 2010-September 2011
      Folder 6: Improving the Partnership Between Private Foundations and Social Welfare Programs, by Samuel J. Silberman (reprinted from Social Work Practice, 1971
      Folder 7: Support for Social Work Education, by Samuel J. Silberman, Samuel L. Hyman, Jack Otis, and Charles Laughton (Council on Social Work Education), 1972
      Folder 8: Meeting Human Service Needs in the Workplace: A Role for Social Work (a report on the April 1-4, 1979 Conference at the Wingspread Conference Center sponsored by Columbia University School of Social Work, Hunter School of Social Work, and Council on Social Work Education), July 1980
      Folder 9: A New Strain for Social Work, address by Samuel J. Silberman, Opening Plenary Session, Annual Meeting, Group for the Advancement of Doctoral Education, Philadelphia, October 10, 1982
      Folder 10: Council on Social Work Education, Thirteenth Annual Program Meeting, Second Plenary Session, Detroit, Michigan, March 12, 1984
      Folder 11: Gaining Perspective on Losing Ground, essay by R. Patti, M. Abramovitz, S. Burghardt, M. Fabricant, M. Haffey, E. Dane, R. Starr, 1987
      Folder 12: Higher Education's Lay Trusteeship: Why Should It Be Protected?, by Samuel J. Silberman, 1987
      Folder 13: The Lois and Samuel Silberman Fund Faculty Awards Program, 1998-1999, 2001-2002
      Materials in Box 3.8.4 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - Silberman Fund (RESTRICTED), 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 3.8.5, Folder 1-3)
      Folder 1: Silberman Fund -- Annual reports, 1970-1986
      Folder 2: Lois and Samuel Silberman Fund, Inc. -- Donation and supporting organization agreement with Community Funds, Inc.; personal advisory memorandum of Samuel J. Silberman with exhibits, March 20, 1992
      Folder 3: Lois and Samuel Silberman Fund, Inc. -- Donation and supporting organization agreement with Community Funds, Inc.; closing and background documents, March 20, 1992
      Engraved shovel: The Hunter College Complex in East Harlem, The Silberman School of Social Work, the CUNY School of Public Health (Planned), the Center for Puerto Rican Studies (CENTRO) Library and Archives, groundbreaking November 16, 2009
      Materials in Box 3.8.5 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
  - Sub-series 9: The September 11th Fund (PARTIALLY RESTRICTED), 2001-2006
    Some materials in Sub-series 9: The September 11th Fund are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - The September 11th Fund: Dockets, Board of Directors (RESTRICTED), November 2001-September 2002 (Offsite-box 3.9.1)
      Materials in Box 3.9.1 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - The September 11th Fund: Dockets, Board of Directors (RESTRICTED), November 2002-December 2004 (Offsite-box 3.9.2)
      Materials in Box 3.9.2 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
    - The September 11th Fund: Reports, publications, speeches, grants (RESTRICTED), 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 3.9.3, Folder 1-13)
      Materials in Box 3.9.3 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
      Folder 1: Board of Directors; Executive Director/CEO; founding documents; briefing document; talking points, testimony of Joshua Gotbaum, Executive Director/CEO; grant approval process; grants made from inception through November 8, 2001, September 11-December 6, 2001
      Folder 2: Process for setting priorities, October 30, 2001
      Folder 3: Unanimous written consents for September 11th Fund, November 2, 2001
      Folder 4: The September 11th Fund: Operational Process Review, PricewaterhouseCoopers LLC, November 8, 2001
      Folder 5:: The September 11th Fund: Implications for Distribution Strategy (report by McKinsey & Company), November 28, 2001
      Folder 6: Early September 11th Fund documents (first board meeting, Cash Assistance Program), December 6, 2001-April 12, 2002
      Folder 7: The September 11th Fund Ongoing Recovery Program, July 11, 2002
      Folder 8: The September 11th Fund One Year Later (illustrated booklet), 2002
      Folder 9: September 11: Interim Report on the Response of Charities (report to Charles Grassley, Committee on Finance, U.S. Senate), 2002
      Folder 10: Giving in the Aftermath of 9/11: An Update on the Foundation and Corporate Response, The Foundation Center, November 2002
      Folder 11: Speeches (Slutsky, DiPerna); interview (Slutsky by Philanthropy New Digest); Ford Foundation report, May 2003; case study by David Hoyt (Stanford Social Innovation Review)
      Folder 12: The September 11th Fund: The First Six Months, 2002
      Folder 13: September 11: Perspectives from the Field of Philathropy, The Foundation Center, 2002
    - The September 11th Fund: Reports, publications, speeches, grants (PARTIALLY RESTRICTED), 2003-2006 (Offsite-box 3.9.4, Folder 1-11)
      Folder 1: The September 11th Fund: Lessons and Strategies for the United Way Network (draft), January 2003
      Folder 2: A Blueprint for Emergency Preparedness by Nonprofits, by the Greater Washington Task Force on Nonprofit Emergency Preparedness, September 2003
      Folder 3: September 11: Perspectives from the Field of Philanthropy, Volume Two, The Foundation Center, 2003
      Folder 4: The September 11th Fund, Year Two 2002-2003, Annual Report, 2003
      Folder 5: A Pig in a Python: How the Charitable Response to September 11 Overwhelmed the Law of Disaster Relief, by Robert A. Katz, Indiana Law Review, vol. 36, no. 2, 2003
      Folder 6: September 11: The Philanthropic Response, The Foundation Center, 2004
      Folder 7: The September 11th Fund: Collaboration and Accountability, Stanford Graduate School of Business, Case Number: PM-50, Version: (A) 02/19/03, February 2003
      Folder 8: The September 11th Fund: Grants for Chinatown, September 2005 (RESTRICTED)
      Folder 9: The September 11th Fund: Final Report, 2005
      Folder 10: O'Reilly Factor (Bill O'Reilly, Host, Fox News Television), Is 9/11 Charity Money Going Where Intended?, September 11, 2006
      Folder 11: "Because You Matter" (poster for 1-800-LIFENET, 24-hour helpline), n.d.
      Materials in Box 3.9.4/Folder 8 are restricted for 50 years after the creation date of the document.
  - Sub-series 10: Photographs, 1953-2018
    - Photographs: Landmark structures and sites, Manhattan, A-F, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.1)
    - Photographs: Landmark structures and sites, Manhattan, G-SA, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.2)
    - Photographs: Landmark structures and sites, Manhattan, SC-Y, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.3)
    - Photographs: Landmark structures and sites, Brooklyn, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.4)
    - Photographs: Landmark structures and sites, Bronx -- Staten Island -- Queens, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.5)
    - Photographs: Landmark structures and sites, residences in Manhattan, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.6)
    - Landmark structures and sites: Events -- photographs, and publications, 1957-1964 (Offsite-box 3.10.7, Folder 1-8)
      Folder 1: History of NYCT's Landmarks Program (plaques on historic buildings), 1957-1970
      Folder 2: Landmarks of New York luncheon at the Waldorf-Astoria, November 21, 1957
      Folder 3: New York Landmarks: An Index of Architecturally Notable Structures in New York City, Fourth Edition, Second Printing, March 1961, c1957 Municipal Art Society
      Folder 4: Ralph Hayes, Director of NYCT and George Nodyne, President of East River Savings Bank, on the occasion of Landmark of New York Plaque Presentation, March 26, 1962
      Folder 5: Dedication of Mildred Ann Williams Floor at Post Hall, YMCA Residence, Brooklyn, October 29, 1964
      Folders 6 and 7: Heritage of New York: Historic Landmark Plaques of the New York Community Trust, preface by Whitney North Seymour, published by Fordham University Press, c1970 (2 copies)
      Folder 8: New York Reviewed, Nineteenth and Early Twentieth Century Photographs from the Collection of the Art Commission (exhibition catalog, October 9, 1985)
    - Photographs: Events, groups, portraits, 1953-2018 (Offsite-box 3.10.8, Folder 1-39)
      Folder 1: Meetings and events during the tenure of Ralph Hayes as Director of New York Community Trust, 1953-1959
      Folder 2: Barbara Preiskel Board retirement dinner, January 18, 1996
      Folder 3: Visit to Spellman College, announcement of $37 million gift, 1999
      Folder 4: United Fund Hospital Gala, October 6, 2008
      Folder 5: Visit to Maramec Spring Park by NYCT Directors (park operated by The James Foundation, St. James, Missouri), n.d.
      Folder 6: NYCT Distribution Committee field trip to Red Hook, Brooklyn -- Green City Force, ca. 2018
      Folder 7: NYCT Distribution Committee, ca. 2000
      Folder 8: NYCT Distribution Committee, 2003
      Folder 9: NYCT Distribution Committee, n.d.
      Folder 10: NYCT Distribution Committee, n.d.
      Folder 11: Westchester Community Foundation Advisory Committee, n.d.
      Folder 12: Altschul, Arthur
      Folder 13: Ballard, Bruce
      Folder 14: Blum, Robert E.
      Folder 15: Detweiler, Frank H.
      Folder 16: Dumpson, James R., 90th birthday party
      Folder 17: Evarts, William
      Folder 18: Fischmann, Charlotte
      Folder 19: Garfinkel, Barry H.
      Folder 20: Gribetz, Judah
      Folder 21: Hayes, Ralph
      Folder 22: Kaufman, Robert M.
      Folder 23: Kimball, Lindsley
      Folder 24: Madden, John B.
      Folder 25: McCarty, Maclyn
      Folder 26: McIntyre, Helen
      Folder 27: Parsons, William